Marc Brown Papers MS148
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Arthur audiovisual material, 1994 -- 2006; 1995 -- 2001; MS148.002; 0.25 Linear Feet; 552 Audiovisual Object(s)
  - Mister Rogers' neighborhood, episode 1743: Go stop go, 1995 -- 2000; MS148.002.506.00001 (Box 506)
  - Arthur and the square dance, 1998; MS148.002.507.00001 (Box 507)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-007#00038-00045.
  - Sue Ellen and the lost diary, 1998; MS148.002.507.00002 (Box 507)
    This date is approximate. Alternative title for episode is Sue Ellen's lost diary. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-008#00029-00036.
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, 2000; MS148.002.508.00001 (Box 508)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-019#00001-00064.
  - MIP promo, 1995-03-30; MS148.002.509.00001; Cinar (Box 509)
    Online, two versions, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in.
  - Line test demo, 1995-04-01; MS148.002.510.00001; Cinar (Box 510)
    Stereo, 57 secs.
  - Composer's pitch, 1995-06-28; MS148.002.511.00001; Cinar (Box 511)
    Stereo.
  - AKOM animation test, 1995-07-07; MS148.002.512.00001; Cinar (Box 512)
  - Preview reel, 1995-12-19; MS148.002.513.00001 (Box 513)
  - Opening sequence, 1996-06-05; MS148.002.514.00001; Cinar (Box 514)
    The opening, for client approval.
  - Opening sequence; bumpers, 1996-06-19; MS148.002.515.00001; Cinar (Box 515)
    Final online picture, mix for approval, stereo.
  - Promo, 1996-10-22; MS148.002.516.00001; Cinar (Box 516)
    Stereo, 5 min.
  - Bumper, sc 7, 1996; MS148.002.517.00001; Cinar (Box 517)
    This date is approximate.
  - Tape loop, 1999-06-04; MS148.002.518.00001 (Box 518)
    60 mins.
  - Arthur special, 2000-05-09; MS148.002.519.00001; Cinar (Box 519)
    Clients, 4 min.
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, 2000-08-03; MS148.002.520.00001 (Box 520)
    RT: 56:02. Home video version.
  - Bumpers, 2000-08-04; MS148.002.521.00001; Cinar (Box 521)
    Bumper fin. for with ret/tk1 1 outst. ret/tk2, offline.
  - Episodes 76-85 bumpers, 2000-09-01; MS148.002.522.00001; Cinar (Box 522)
    Mix for approval, stereo English mix, TC burn-in.
  - Michelle Kwan bumper, 2001-10-09; MS148.002.523.00001; Cinar (Box 523)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2: full stereo mix, TC burn-in.
  - It's only rock 'n' roll, starring the Backstreet Boys, 2002-07-31; MS148.002.525.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 525)
    RT: 56: 46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-022#00020-00047. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-184#00001. Associated NTSC/Stereo tape can be found at MS158/002-551. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00006-00008.
  - 806: Postcards from Buster, part I, 2003-10-07; MS148.002.526.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 526)
    Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00034-00036. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-574#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-192#00001 and MS148/002-193#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-481#00001, MS148/002-482#00001, MS148/002-483#00001, and MS148/002-527#00001. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00019.
  - 806: Postcards from Buster, part II, 2003-10-07; MS148.002.526.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 526)
    Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00043-00045.
  - 806: Postcards from Buster, part I, 2003-10-07; MS148.002.527.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 527)
    Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00034-00036. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-574#00001. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-574#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-192#00001 and MS148/002-193#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-481#00001, MS148/002-482#00001, MS148/002-483#00001, and MS148/002-526#00001. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00019.
  - 806: Postcards from Buster, part II, 2003-10-07; MS148.002.527.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 527)
  - 125A: The "A" team, 2005-02-01; MS148.002.528.00001; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 528)
    Length: 22:24, ch1: guide track, ch2: guide track, mix for approval, copy TCBI. No associated production files.
  - 125B: Buster the myth maker, 2005-02-01; MS148.002.528.00002; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 528)
  - 806: Postcards from Buster, part II, 2003-04-28; MS148.002.529.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 529)
    Live action sequence, RT: 8:36. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00043-00045.
  - 19A: Buster's new friend, 1996-06-12; MS148.002.530.00001; Cinar (Box 530)
    Mix for approval, final online, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00070-00075. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00018. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-058#00001. Associated tape can be found at MS148/002-248#00002 and MS148/002-249#00002.
  - 19B: Arthur's baby, 1996-06-12; MS148.002.530.00002; Cinar (Box 530)
    Mix for approval, final online, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00073 and MS148/001-004#00001-00003. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-058#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-244#00001 and MS148/002-245#00001.
  - 21A: D.W.'s baby, 1996-07-02; MS148.002.531.00001; Cinar (Box 531)
    Mix for approval, final online, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00015-00019. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00020. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-244#00002 and MS148/002-245#00002.
  - 21B: Arthur the wrecker, 1996-07-02; MS148.002.531.00002; Cinar (Box 531)
    Mix for approval, final online, audio Ch1. Ch2., TC Burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00020-00024. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00020. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-531#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-250#00001, MS148/002-251#00001, and MS148/002-252#00001.
  - 22A: D.W. gets lost, 1996-07-08; MS148.002.532.00001; Cinar (Box 532)
    Mix for approval, final online, audio Ch1. Ch2., TC Burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00025-00028. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00021. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-061#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-271#00002 and MS148/002-272#00002.
  - 22B: Arthur's lost library book, 1996-07-08; MS148.002.532.00002; Cinar (Box 532)
    Mix for approval, final online, audio Ch1. Ch2., TC Burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00029-00034. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00021. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-061#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-230#00002 and MS148/002-231#00002.
  - 23A: D.W. the copycat, 1996-07-09; MS148.002.533.00001; Cinar (Box 533)
    Mix for approval, online (one retake missing), audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00035-00039. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00022. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-062#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-232#00002 and MS148/002-233#00002.
  - 23B: D.W. flips, 1996-07-09; MS148.002.533.00002; Cinar (Box 533)
    Mix for approval, online (one retake missing), audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00040-00045. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00022. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-062#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-255#00002 and MS148/002-256#00002.
  - 24A: Sick as a dog, 1996-07-24; MS148.002.534.00001; Cinar (Box 534)
    Mix for approval, final online, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00046-00052. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00023. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-063#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-259#00002 and MS148/002-260#00002.
  - 24B: Arthur makes the team, 1996-07-24; MS148.002.534.00002; Cinar (Box 534)
    Mix for approval, final online, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00053-00055. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00023. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-063#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-261#00002 and MS148/002-262#00002.
  - 25A: Team trouble, 1996-07-29; MS148.002.535.00001; Cinar (Box 535)
    Mix for approval, final online, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00056-00061. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-267#00002 and MS148/002-268#00002.
  - 25B: The perfect brother, 1996-07-29; MS148.002.535.00002; Cinar (Box 535)
    Mix for approval, final online, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00062-00068. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#000024. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-265#00002 and MS148/002-265#00002.
  - 26A: Misfortune teller, 1996-06-14; MS148.002.536.00001; Cinar (Box 536)
    Offline 1st cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00069-00076. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00025. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-537#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-269#00002 and MS148/002-270#00002.
  - 26B: The half-baked sale, 1996-06-14; MS148.002.536.00002; Cinar (Box 536)
    Offline 1st cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00001-00005. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00024. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-537#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-263#00002 and MS148/002-264#00002.
  - 26A: Misfortune teller, 1996-08-06; MS148.002.537.00001; Cinar (Box 537)
    Mix for approval, final approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00069-00076. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00025. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-536#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-269#00002 and MS148/002-270#00002.
  - 26B: The half-baked sale, 1996-08-06; MS148.002.537.00002; Cinar (Box 537)
    Mix for approval, final approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00001-00005. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00024. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-536#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-263#00002 and MS148/002-264#00002.
  - 27A: Arthur cleans up, 1996-06-26; MS148.002.538.00001; Cinar (Box 538)
    Offline 1st cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00006-00011. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00026. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-539#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-273#00002 and MS148/002-274#00002.
  - 27B: Sue Ellen moves in, 1996-06-26; MS148.002.538.00002; Cinar (Box 538)
    Offline 1st cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00012-00018. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00026. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-539#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-265#00001 and MS148/002-266#00001.
  - 27A: Arthur cleans up, 1996-08-12; MS148.002.539.00001; Cinar (Box 539)
    Mix for approval, final approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00006-00011. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00026. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-538#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-273#00002 and MS148/002-274#00002.
  - 27B: Sue Ellen moves in, 1996-08-12; MS148.002.539.00002; Cinar (Box 539)
    Mix for approval, final approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00012-00018. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00026. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-538#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-265#00001 and MS148/002-266#00001.
  - 28A: Arthur's substitute teacher trouble, 1996-07-03; MS148.002.540.00001; Cinar (Box 540)
    Offline 1st cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00019-00025. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00027. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-277#00002 and MS148/002-278-00002.
  - 28B: I'm a poet, 1996-07-03; MS148.002.540.00002; Cinar (Box 540)
    Offline 1st cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00026-00030 and MS148/001-005#00032-00034. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00027. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-279#00001.
  - 29A: Arthur's New Year's Eve, 1996-07-23; MS148.002.541.00001; Cinar (Box 541)
    Offline 1st cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00035-00042. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00028. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-064#00001. Associated tape can be found at MS148/002-281#00002.
  - 29B: Poor Muffy, 1996-07-23; MS148.002.541.00002; Cinar (Box 541)
    Offline 1st cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00043-00049. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00028. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-064#00002. Associated tape can be found at MS148/002-275#00002 and MS148/002-276#00002.
  - 38A: Arthur makes a movie, 1997-07-04; MS148.002.542.00001; Cinar (Box 542)
    Offline 1st cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00080-00081 and MS148/001-007#00001-00004. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-078#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-291#00001 and MS148/002-292#00001.
  - 38B: Play it again, D.W., 1997-07-04; MS148.002.542.00002; Cinar (Box 542)
    Offline 1st cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-007#00005-00011. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-078#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-295#00002 and MS148/002-296#00002.
  - Bumper animation only, 1997-07-22; MS148.002.543.00001; Cinar (Box 543)
  - 40A: Lost!, 1997-07-29; MS148.002.544.00001; Cinar (Box 544)
    Offline 1st cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-007#00026-00032. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-079#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-302#00001 and MS148/002-303#00001.
  - 40B: The short, quick summer, 1997-07-29; MS148.002.544.00002; Cinar (Box 544)
    Offline 1st cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-007#00033-00037. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-079#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-302#00002 and MS148/002-303#00002.
  - 72A: 1001 dads, 1999-08-18; MS148.002.545.00001; Cinar (Box 545)
    Online (no retakes missing), mix for approval, stereo English mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00073-00082. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-141#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-382#00001 and MS148/002-383#00001. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00001.
  - 72B: Prunella's prediction, 1999-08-18; MS148.002.545.00002; Cinar (Box 545)
    Online (no retakes missing), mix for approval, stereo English mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00083-00089 and MS148/001-014#00001-00003. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-141#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-382#00002 and MS148/002-383#00002. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00001.
  - 73A: The blizzard, 1999-08-26; MS148.002.546.00001; Cinar (Box 546)
    Online (no retakes missing), mix for approval, stereo English mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00004-00012. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-142#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-374#00001, MS148/002-375#00001, and MS148/002-376#00001. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00002.
  - 73B: What is that thing?, 1999-08-26; MS148.002.546.00002; Cinar (Box 546)
    Online (no retakes missing), mix for approval, stereo English mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00013-00020. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-142#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-384#00001, MS148/002-385#00001, and MS148/002-386#00001. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00002.
  - 75A: Buster's best behavior, 1999-08-26; MS148.002.547.00001; Cinar (Box 547)
    First cut for clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00040-00049. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-145#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-146#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-384#00002, MS148/002-385#00002, and MS148/002-386#00002. Additional notes for this tape were removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00003.
  - 75B: My music rules, 1999-08-26; MS148.002.547.00002; Cinar (Box 547)
    First cut for clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00048-00057. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-145#00002. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-146#00002 and MS148/002-129#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-387#00001 and MS148/002-388#00001. Additional notes for this tape were removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00003.
  - 87A: Best of the nest, 2001-06-01; MS148.002.548.00001; Cinar (Box 548)
    First cut for clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-018#00043-00047. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-410#00002 and MS148/002-411#00002. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00004.
  - 87B: The secret life of dogs and babies, 2001-06-01; MS148.002.548.00002; Cinar (Box 548)
    First cut for clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-018#00048-00053. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-414#00002, MS148/002-415#00002, and MS148/002-416#00002. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00004.
  - 88A: Arthur plays the blues, 2001-06-15; MS148.002.549.00001; Cinar (Box 549)
    First cut for clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-018#00054-00058. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-412#00001 and MS148/002-413#00001. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00005.
  - 88B: Buster's sweet success, 2001-06-15; MS148.002.549.00002; Cinar (Box 549)
    First cut for clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-018#00059-00065. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-412#00002 and MS148/002-413#00002. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00005.
  - Bumpers, 2001-06-29; MS148.002.550.00001; Cinar (Box 550)
    For visual approval, no sound, TC burn-in.
  - It's only rock 'n' roll, 2001-08-07; MS148.002.551.00001; Cinar (Box 551)
    NTSC/Stereo. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-022#00020-00047. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-184#00001. Associated tape can be found at MS148/002-525#00001. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00006-00008.
  - 89A: Muffy's soccer shocker, 2001-06-29; MS148.002.552.00001; Cinar (Box 552)
    First cut for clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00001-00004. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-176#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-417#00001, MS148/002-418#00001, and MS148/002-419#00001. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00006.
  - 89B: The boy who cried comet, 2001-06-29; MS148.002.552.00002; Cinar (Box 552)
    First cut for clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00005-00008. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-176#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-420#00001 and MS148/002-421#00001. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00006.
  - 90A: Brother, can you spare a clarinet?, 2001-07-13; MS148.002.553.00001; Cinar (Box 553)
    First cut for clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00018-00022. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-177#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-417#00002, MS148/002-418#00002, and MS148/002-419#00002. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00007.
  - 90B: Prunella's special edition, 2001-07-13; MS148.002.553.00002; Cinar (Box 553)
    First cut for clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00023-00027. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-177#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-414#00001, MS148/002-415#00001, and MS148/002-416#00001. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00007.
  - 92A: The boy with his head in the clouds, 2001; MS148.002.554.00001; Cinar (Box 554)
    This date is approximate. First cut for clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00039-00040 and MS148/001-021#00001-00004, and MS148/001-021#00010-00011. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-179#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-425#00001, MS148/002-426#00001, and MS148/002-427#00001. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00008.
  - 92B: Citizen Frensky, 2001; MS148.002.554.00002; Cinar (Box 554)
    This date is approximate. First cut for clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#00005-00011. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-179#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-422#00001, MS148/002-423#00001, and MS148/002-424#00001. A page of edit notes for this tape was removed and rehoused in MS148/002-578#00008.
  - 99A: Is there a doctor in the house?, 2002-07-24; MS148.002.555.00001; Cinar (Box 555)
    Mix for approval, tr. 1-2: full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#00009-00012. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-458#00002, MS148/002-459#00002, and MS148/002-460#00002. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00005.
  - 99B: Pick a car, any car, 2002-07-24; MS148.002.555.00002; Cinar (Box 555)
    Mix for approval, tr. 1-2: full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#000013-00014, 00017-00019. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-452#00001, MS148/002-453#00001, and MS148/002-454#00001. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00005.
  - Larry King interstitial, 2002-08-07; MS148.002.556.00001; Cinar (Box 556)
    Offline for approval, audio ch1-2, TC burn-in.
  - 100A: Don't ask Muffy, 2002-07-15; MS148.002.557.00001; Cinar (Box 557)